STANISLAV ALEXOVIČ

Software developer

■ stanislav.alexovic@gmail.com ● Slovakia, EU

Profile

With 15 years of experience as a seasoned programmer, my career objective is to develop clean and readable programs, placing a strong emphasis on understanding underlying functionality to ensure efficient program design implementation. I am highly motivated to continuously expand my knowledge abreast of stay emerging 1 technologies. Moreover, am passionate about sharing my expertise and actively collaborating with others to cultivate a culture of knowledge exchange and growth.

Skills

- C++
- Python
- ROS, ROS2
- RabbitMQ
- Docker
- Git
- Visual Studio Code
- Linux

Education

Technical University of Košice,
 Master's degree, Computer Science

Experience

Photoneo / Brightpick

= 10/2019 − PRESENT

Senior software developer

- Create fleet management for automatic warehouse system.
 Coordination and management of multiple mobile robots.
 # Python
- Developing software for mobile robot. API, communication with hardware, processing inputs from sensors, localization of pose. # C++, ROS, Docker, SLAM

ComAp

iii 10/2018 – 10/2019

Embedded programmer

- Implementing PLC interpreter and PLC blocks. # C
- Refactoring MODBUD client. # C, MODBUS

ESET

iii 09/2008 – 10/2018

Software developer

- Create push notification system. Client part and MQTT protocol implementation. # C++, MQTT
- Maintained integration of antispam engine into ESET Smart Security product. # C, C++
- Created DNS tunnel module which could transfer data over DNS if other network protocol were forbidden. # C++
- Created web based IS which handled incoming antispam statistics. Processing, storing, filtering, showing. # Python, HTML, CSS, SQL
- Implemented Standalone application for creating live CD/DVD or USB system. ESET SysRescue Live. # C++, QT
- Developed standalone application for activation preinstalled ESET products. # C++, MFC
- Maintained installer for ESET products. # C++, MSI, WiX